advanceduninstaller.com 2019-06-09

# Privacy - Advanced Uninstaller PRO

##  Your consent

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

##  GDPR Compliance

Advanced Uninstaller PRO collects, uses and processes its users' data. Some data, such as username or e-mail address, is provided directly by the users, and some of it is collected by Advanced Uninstaller PRO, in order to ensure efficient functionality. We believe in transparency towards our users and take responsibility when it comes to respecting your privacy.

We value the vital role of personal data protection and we give you the assurance that you are guaranteed the following rights:

  * \- Access to your personal data that we possess;
  *  
  * \- Personal data portability;
  *  
  * \- Decision over the processing of your personal data;
  *  
  * \- Correction of your personal data.
  *  
  * \- The right to be forgotten.
  *  

##  What information do we collect

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

##  What do we use your information for

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

\- To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

\- To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

\- To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

\- To process transactions purchased product or service requested

\- To send periodic emails

The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

##  How do we protect your information ?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. 

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

##  Do we disclose any information to outside parties ?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

##  California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

##  Changes to our privacy policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

##  Do we use cookies ?

Yes. What is a cookie? A "cookie" is a small text file that is stored by your web browser on your computer or mobile device.

We use cookies to help identify your computer so we can tailor your user experience, track shopping basket contents and remember where you are in the order process.

You can disable any cookies already stored on your computer, but these may stop our website from functioning properly.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
